Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 52: Communications Workers - Phone Workers sign cards for Teamsters Membership, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 53: Illinois Telephone Accounting employees, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 54: Communications Workers - Our Last Word, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 55: Communications Workers - Our Last Word, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 56: Communications Workers - The Company game, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 57: Communications Workers - The McClellan Story, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 58: Communications Workers - The McClellan Story, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 59: Communications Workers - Telephone Plant Workers, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 60: Communications Workers - Telephone Plant Workers, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 61: Communications Workers - Some reasons why Telephone Workers are voting to join Teamsters, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 62: Communications Workers - Some reasons why Telephone Workers are voting to join Teamsters, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 63: Spotlight on labor leaders, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 64: Let's meet our dead-line with new NLRB, 1963; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Author: Harold J. Gibbons
    Notes: Includes letter on reverse.
  - Item 65: Do you need more money?, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 66: Gibbons Challenges Beirne, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 67: Teamsters charge election fraud, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 68: To all Westchester, Manhattan trunk facilities, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 69: Company unionism in action!, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 70: At & T exposed!, 1963; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 71: New York Telephone ompany attempts to frame 2 employees to give CWA the NLRB election by seeking perjured statements from Switchman, 1964; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 72: Because the Teamsters-Communications Division has been confident all along of victory., 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Author: Al Weiss
  - Item 73: I have been asked by members of the Brotherhood to comment on the position taken by the Communication Workres of America, 1961; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Author: G. D. Gleason
  - Item 74: How to win strikes: lessons from the 1934 Minneapolis Truckers Strike by Harry DeBoer, 1994; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Author: Harry DeBoer
  - Item 75: Resolution, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Notes: October 9, 1962.
  - Item 76: As you know, we have been conducting an organizing campaign, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 77: I've been instructed from Washington to keep you fully informed, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Author: William P. Genoese
  - Item 78: New York Telephone Company Plant Department, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 79: Telephone Tape Locations in State of New York, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 80: The Day of Decision is here., Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Notes: Action-Gram
  - Item 81: Attention N. Y. Plant Telephone Workers, 1963; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 82: Women Workers, Beware!, 1963; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 83: Two Slilces or a Whole Loaf?, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 84: The Inside Story: Why Doesn't Management Like the Teamsters?, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 85: Phony CWA Promises Bared in Baltimore, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 86: Who's Paying for this Operation?, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 87: Who's Paying for this Operation?, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 88: Baby Blue, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 89: Questions and Answers., 1967; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Author: Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania
    Notes: Texts, no.521
  - Item 90: Questions and Answers., 1967; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Notes: Texts, no.521. Copy 2.
  - Item 91: Informal, NLRB Conference, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
    Author: Ken Silvers
  - Item 92: Don't Worry About Your Job Ratios, Men. Just Give the Teamsters Hell., Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 93: The Key is Now in Your Hand, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 94: The Key is Now in Your Hand, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 95: This Money Belongs to You. Don't Walk Away From It!, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 96: This Money Belongs to You. Don't Walk Away From It!, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
  - Item 97: Strike Three, and You Are Really Out!, Publication (Box 602, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 602, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Constituion, 1986; Publication (Box 602, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Constituion, 1986; Publication (Box 602, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Constituion, 1991; Publication (Box 602, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Constituion, 1991; Publication (Box 602, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: L'International Teamster, 1986; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1986:Mar.). Copy 2.
    Language: French.
  - Item 2: The National Warehouse Division of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1986; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The National Warehouse Division of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1986; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: L'International Teamster, 1986; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1986).
  - Item 5: Report XXXVI to all members of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Oct/Nov. 1992), Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Report XXXVI to all members of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (Oct/Nov. 1992), Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Cooking without walnuts., 1992; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
    Author: Jeannette Ferrary
    Notes: cook book
  - Item 8: IBT focus on stewards, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Appellate Litigation Arising from John Cunningham, et al. v. John F. English, et al. Civil Action No. 2361-57 -- United States District Court for the District of Columbia, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: BulletinRon Carey wins Presidency in great historic victory in IBT elections, 1991; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: 24th Convention of the. Report of Committee Rules.., Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: 24th Convention of the. Report of Committee Rules.., Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: 24th Convention of the .Resolutions, 1991; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: 24th Convention of the .Resolutions, 1991; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Official Results of the 1991 IBT Election, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Official Results of the 1991 IBT Election, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Ron Carey Slate - '96, 1996; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
    Notes: Bumper sticker
  - Item 18: Ask us what we can do for you, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Drug & Alcohol abuse program, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Governmental Affairs, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Governmental Affairs, Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: L'International Teamster, 1986; Publication (Box 602, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1986:Mar.)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1962:July 31)
  - Item 2: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1962:Aug. 6)
  - Item 3: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1962:Aug. 9)
  - Item 4: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1962:Aug. 15)
  - Item 5: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1962:Aug. 23)
  - Item 6: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1962:Aug. 29)
  - Item 7: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1962:Sep. 11)
  - Item 8: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1962:Sep. 13)
  - Item 9: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.10 (1962:Sep. 21)
  - Item 10: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.11 (1962:Oct. 2)
  - Item 11: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.12 (1962:Oct. 5)
  - Item 12: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.14 (1962:Oct. 12)
  - Item 13: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.15 (1962:Oct. 17)
  - Item 14: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.16 (1962:Oct. 19)
  - Item 15: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.17 (1962:Oct. 23)
  - Item 16: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.18 (1962:Oct. 24)
  - Item 17: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.19 (1962:Oct. 25)
  - Item 18: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.20 (1962:Oct. 25)
  - Item 19: General Electric Teamster Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.21 (1962:Oct. 31)
  - Item 20: The Philadelphia Story, 1960; Publication (Box 602, Folder 7)
    Author: Richardson Dilworth
    Notes: Editorial
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Your employer will never see these signed cards, Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
    Author: Teamsters' Joint Council no.54
  - Item 2: Ability to earn your most valuable asset, Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: It's your baby, secret ballot, Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: A normal employer reaction when employees organize, Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Iniation fees? Union dues? What will it cost to join the union?, Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: It can be done, Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Ability to earn your most valuable asset..., Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: This letter is to acknowledge, with thanks, receipt of your signed authorization card., Publication (Box 602, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Ask the man who owns one - A Teamster Card J-M Waterville, Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
    Author: Johns Manville Organizing Committee, Teamsters Local 20
  - Item 2: Ask the man who owns one - A Teamster Card J-M Waterville, Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: They are treating you like children!, Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Look at your take-home pay!, 1965; Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Look at your take-home pay!, 1965; Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Why do I want to join the Teamsters Union?, Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Bulletin to all J-M Waterville Workers, 1965; Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Team and Wheel, 1965; Publication (Box 602, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.20:no.20 (1965:Oct. 30)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A single employee is helpless, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
    Author: Whirlpool Organizing Committee, Teamsters Local 40
  - Item 2: Whats all this fuss about the Teamsters?, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Without Job security you have nothing, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Whirlpool employees, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Promises Promises, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: To All Whirlpool employees We Wish You a Very Joyous, Happy and Prosperous Holiday Season, 1965; Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Whirlpool employees, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
    Author: Paul Amerine
  - Item 8: Employees of Whirlpool Corporation Marion Division, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Whirlpool employees of Marion, Ohio, Publication (Box 602, Folder 10)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Next Friday, October 11, 1963 you will be asked to vote in an election. You will be asked to mark you ballot for or against Teamster Union representation, Publication (Box 603, Folder 1)
    Author: Teamsters Local 7
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Dear Telephone Workers, Publication (Box 603, Folder 2)
    Author: John J. O'Rourke
  - Item 2: A personal message from John L. O'Rourke, Publication (Box 603, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: District 50 doesn't fool Hoben workers either!!, 1964; Publication (Box 603, Folder 3)
    Author: Teamsters Local 50
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Teamsters win election, 1958; Publication (Box 603, Folder 4)
    Notes: news clipping
  - Item 2: Tally of Ballots, 1958; Publication (Box 603, Folder 4)
    Author: Lancashire Textile Processing Corporation; TWUA (Textile Workers Union of America)
  - Item 3: Cerification of Representatives, 1958; Publication (Box 603, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Roll Towards Progress with "Jason and his Union On Wheels", Publication (Box 603, Folder 4)
    Author: Teamsters Local 59
  - Item 5: Why Didn't You Tell the Truth, Carignan?, Publication (Box 603, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Lancashire Textile Workers, Ask Yourself the Following Questions, Publication (Box 603, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The Sour Notes Played by the Distorting Troubador, Carignan, Publication (Box 603, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: How to win strikes: a union strike manual, 1979; Publication (Box 603, Folder 5)
    Author: Teamsters Union Local No. 115.
  - Item 2: How to win strikes: a union strike manual, 1979; Publication (Box 603, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: For higher wages and better working conditions, vote YES, Publication (Box 603, Folder 6)
    Author: Teamsters United Paper and Allied Workers
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Crafts side against Brewery Workers in current Controversy, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: Toledo Blade
  - Item 2: Decision unanimous: no-rad stand pact reaffirmed by L-M-C, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: The Labor Union
  - Item 3: National AFL-CIO organizers to aid Brewery Local in affiliation dispute, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Court rejects Teamsters plea, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Council backs L-M-C attack on Brewery Union, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Union Council Chief attacked, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Teamsters hit beating case insiuations..., 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Quit AFL-CIO Council, 21 unions urged..., 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: VOTE! Teamsters..., 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Building Trades Quitting Council, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Catchy labels on assembly bills worth their weight in floor votes, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Close ranks, Ballard urges unions, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Dairymen hear Teamster, Brewery eloquence as NLRB vote nears, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Brewery workers sue Teamsters for libel, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: Toledo Times
  - Item 15: Dairymen voting to pick union, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Dairymen Vote, 363-99, to stay in Teamsters, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: All for 99 Votes!, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Teamsters rejected, 2-1, in Findlay Brewery vote..., 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Vote of confidence accorded Local 361 by margin of 4 to 1, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: Union nonraiding agreement periled by move of Sealtest employees, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Revolt against Teamsters is barely holding its own, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: Ken Clawson
  - Item 22: AFL-CIO threatened by Sealtest bolt, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Labor Council declines to enforce no-raiding policy in Dairy disputes, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: Meany urges Board to shun no-raid pact..., 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: Teamsters Dairy Chief resigns in member rift, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: Teamsters unity voiced at Dairy local meeting, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 27: Msgr. Doyle backs no-raiding pact, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 28: Union adds two Dairy vote bids..., 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 29: L-M-C told to quit aiding Teamsters, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 30: Special meeting of L-M-C called, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 31: LMC committee statement condemns raiding tactics of Brewery workers, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: Toledo Monitor
  - Item 32: Teamsters ask Brewery vote, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 33: Union organizing drive to continue at Dairies, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 34: No-raid stand reversed by Union Council, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 35: L-M-C leasers support Teamsters in Union rift, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 36: Teamsters clear way for Dairy Worker vote, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 37: Dairy workers labor vote set for March 16th, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 38: Dairy Workers News: The UBW Dairy Workers Division is selling swiss cheese, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: Teamsters Joint Council 44
  - Item 39: Dairy Workers News: UW-AFL-CIO join hands with Teamsters in fight to preserve integrity of Toledo Labor climate, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: Teamsters Joint Council 44; Charles Ballard
  - Item 40: Dairy Workers News: Hey Feller, you never told us about this, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 41: EXTRA WSPD announced Tuesday, March 9: A Toledo Legislator is going to introduce a bill in the Ohio House.., Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 42: FLASH The city of Toledo, meeting today (March 8th) in regular session, unanimously endorsed a resolution of the Labor-Management-Citizens Committee which condemns the raid of the Cinncinati Brewery Workers, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: Teamsters Local 361
  - Item 43: Dairy Workers News: Some simple questions for the BWU smear squad, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 44: Dairy Workers News: Got a beef?..., 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 45: Correspondence - In a letter to the Toledo Teamsters., 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: Lawrence N. Steinberg
  - Item 46: Group Exhibit "B" National Labor Relations Board Filings, Orders, etc., Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Teamsters
  - Item 47: Group Exhibit "D" UBW Leaflets and Handbills, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 48: Group Exhibit "H" Financial and Personnel, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 49: Tare Dairy Companies Case Number 8-RC-5833, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Notes: Telegram
  - Item 50: This is the AFL-CIO Saying "Welcome Home", Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: AFL-CIO
  - Item 51: Why The Boss Just Loves Teamsters, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 52: Self Pride, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 53: Wake Up and Think, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 54: Greatest Employees, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 55: Building Trades Vote Teamsters Full Support, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 56: The High Cost of Non-Union Dues, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: George T. Brown
  - Item 57: It's Your Money!, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 58: Facts and News: A Positive Program for 1965, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
    Author: UBW (United Brewery Workers)
  - Item 59: Reform, It's Wonderful, or Is It?, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 60: Facts and News: Haven't You Had Enough?, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 61: Dairy Workers Division UBW, AFL-CIO, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 62: Sure, You've Got a Beef!, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 63: Facts and News: Organizing Committee, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 64: Facts and News: Teamsters Admit Past Failures, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 65: Facts and News: Lies Backfire, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 66: Facts and News: We Believe in Integrity and Honesty, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 67: Dear Toledo Dairy Workers, Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
  - Item 68: Get a Clear Picture, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Special Attention All Hershey Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 603, Folder 8)
    Author: Teamsters Local 386
  - Item 2: Special Attention All Hershey Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 603, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Hersheyism Demands, Publication (Box 603, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: The Real Issue in Your Campaign, Publication (Box 603, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Major Users of Milk in this Area for Manufacturing Milk Food Products, Publication (Box 603, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Hersheyism Is Running Scared, Publication (Box 603, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 603, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Please take notice of the following meeting for Nomination and Election o fOficers an dBusiness Agents of Local 584 for a Nomination meeting, 1978; Publication (Box 603, Folder 9)
    Author: Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees Local 584
  - Item 2: General Membership meetings of Local No. 619 have been cancelled for the months of June, July and August, 1965; Publication (Box 603, Folder 9)